{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766810054","data":{"timestamp":" 947766810053"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GRACA"," userResponse":" GRACA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766811211","data":{"timestamp":" 947766811210"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIZALIWA"," userResponse":" ALIZALIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766812250","data":{"timestamp":" 947766812249"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOZAMBIQUE"," userResponse":" MOZAMBIQUE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766822373","data":{"timestamp":" 947766822372"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GRACA"," userResponse":" GRACA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766824250","data":{"timestamp":" 947766824250"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIZALIWA"," userResponse":" ALIZALIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766825478","data":{"timestamp":" 947766825478"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MOZAMBIQUE"," userResponse":" START_MOZAMBIQUE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766827809","data":{"timestamp":" 947766827808"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOZAMBIQUE"," userResponse":" MOZAMBIQUE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766829537","data":{"timestamp":" 947766829536"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHI"," userResponse":" NCHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766829971","data":{"timestamp":" 947766829971"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" YAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766830760","data":{"timestamp":" 947766830759"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766831508","data":{"timestamp":" 947766831507"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASKINI"," userResponse":" MASKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766832298","data":{"timestamp":" 947766832297"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766832994","data":{"timestamp":" 947766832991"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766833927","data":{"timestamp":" 947766833927"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUWA"," userResponse":" HAWAKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766834798","data":{"timestamp":" 947766834798"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEPATA"," userResponse":" WAMEPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766835474","data":{"timestamp":" 947766835474"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UHURU"," userResponse":" UHURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766837415","data":{"timestamp":" 947766837414"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NCHI"," userResponse":" NCHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766838621","data":{"timestamp":" 947766838621"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" NCHI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766839914","data":{"timestamp":" 947766839913"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" YAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766841422","data":{"timestamp":" 947766841421"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIZALIWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766844966","data":{"timestamp":" 947766844966"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766845472","data":{"timestamp":" 947766845472"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASKINI"," userResponse":" MASKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766845946","data":{"timestamp":" 947766845946"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766846372","data":{"timestamp":" 947766846371"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766846849","data":{"timestamp":" 947766846849"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUWA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766847983","data":{"timestamp":" 947766847982"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUWA"," userResponse":" HAWAKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766848763","data":{"timestamp":" 947766848762"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEPATA"," userResponse":" START_WAMEPATA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766850806","data":{"timestamp":" 947766850806"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEPATA"," userResponse":" START_WAMEPATA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766852501","data":{"timestamp":" 947766852499"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMEPATA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766853891","data":{"timestamp":" 947766853891"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" UHURU"," userResponse":" START_WAMEPATA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766856198","data":{"timestamp":" 947766856198"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UHURU"," userResponse":" UHURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766858164","data":{"timestamp":" 947766858164"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766859217","data":{"timestamp":" 947766859213"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUA"," userResponse":" HAWAKUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766859454","data":{"timestamp":" 947766859453"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766860028","data":{"timestamp":" 947766860027"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766860646","data":{"timestamp":" 947766860645"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NZURI"," userResponse":" NZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766860873","data":{"timestamp":" 947766860873"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766861562","data":{"timestamp":" 947766861562"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766863660","data":{"timestamp":" 947766863660"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766866972","data":{"timestamp":" 947766866972"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766869545","data":{"timestamp":" 947766869545"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWAKUA"," userResponse":" HAWAKUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766869549","data":{"timestamp":" 947766869549"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766869860","data":{"timestamp":" 947766869860"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766869864","data":{"timestamp":" 947766869864"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NZURI"," userResponse":" NZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766870158","data":{"timestamp":" 947766870158"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766870651","data":{"timestamp":" 947766870651"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766872565","data":{"timestamp":" 947766872564"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" MAMAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766873371","data":{"timestamp":" 947766873371"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766873606","data":{"timestamp":" 947766873606"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766874216","data":{"timestamp":" 947766874215"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOTO"," userResponse":" NDOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766874423","data":{"timestamp":" 947766874422"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766875152","data":{"timestamp":" 947766875151"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAPA"," userResponse":" KUWAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766875814","data":{"timestamp":" 947766875813"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWE"," userResponse":" WANAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766877064","data":{"timestamp":" 947766877064"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAISHA"," userResponse":" MAISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766878176","data":{"timestamp":" 947766878175"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZURI"," userResponse":" MAZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766879040","data":{"timestamp":" 947766879039"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766879432","data":{"timestamp":" 947766879431"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766880457","data":{"timestamp":" 947766880456"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASOMO"," userResponse":" MASOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766882291","data":{"timestamp":" 947766882290"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAINGEWEZEKANA"," userResponse":" HAINGEWEZEKANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766884360","data":{"timestamp":" 947766884360"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMAKE"," userResponse":" MAMAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766885823","data":{"timestamp":" 947766885823"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766886066","data":{"timestamp":" 947766886066"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766887968","data":{"timestamp":" 947766887968"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOTO"," userResponse":" NDOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766888371","data":{"timestamp":" 947766888371"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766889269","data":{"timestamp":" 947766889268"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWAPA"," userResponse":" KUWAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766890377","data":{"timestamp":" 947766890376"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWE"," userResponse":" WANAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766891939","data":{"timestamp":" 947766891939"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAISHA"," userResponse":" WANAWE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766893839","data":{"timestamp":" 947766893839"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAISHA"," userResponse":" MAISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766894574","data":{"timestamp":" 947766894574"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZURI"," userResponse":" MAZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766895042","data":{"timestamp":" 947766895042"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766895541","data":{"timestamp":" 947766895540"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766896457","data":{"timestamp":" 947766896457"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASOMO"," userResponse":" MASOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766897419","data":{"timestamp":" 947766897418"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HAINGEWEZEKANA"," userResponse":" START_HAINGEWEZEKANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766898424","data":{"timestamp":" 947766898424"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HAINGEWEZEKANA"," userResponse":" NZURI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766900581","data":{"timestamp":" 947766900581"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamake alikuwa na ndoto ya kuwapa wanawe maisha mazuri lakini bila masomo haingewezekana."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAINGEWEZEKANA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766902811","data":{"timestamp":" 947766902804"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIKI"," userResponse":" WIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766902940","data":{"timestamp":" 947766902940"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHACHE"," userResponse":" CHACHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766903349","data":{"timestamp":" 947766903349"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766903526","data":{"timestamp":" 947766903525"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766903607","data":{"timestamp":" 947766903606"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIFO"," userResponse":" KIFO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766903857","data":{"timestamp":" 947766903856"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766904042","data":{"timestamp":" 947766904042"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABAKE"," userResponse":" BABAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766904708","data":{"timestamp":" 947766904707"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766905084","data":{"timestamp":" 947766905083"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPEWA"," userResponse":" ALIPEWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766905572","data":{"timestamp":" 947766905572"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINA"," userResponse":" JINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766905627","data":{"timestamp":" 947766905627"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUAMBATA"," userResponse":" KUAMBATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766905985","data":{"timestamp":" 947766905985"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766906538","data":{"timestamp":" 947766906537"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UREMBO"," userResponse":" UREMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766906560","data":{"timestamp":" 947766906560"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766913000","data":{"timestamp":" 947766912999"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WIKI"," userResponse":" KIFO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766914981","data":{"timestamp":" 947766914979"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIKI"," userResponse":" WIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766916688","data":{"timestamp":" 947766916687"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHACHE"," userResponse":" CHACHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766917055","data":{"timestamp":" 947766917055"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766917392","data":{"timestamp":" 947766917392"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766918673","data":{"timestamp":" 947766918673"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIFO"," userResponse":" KIFO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766918677","data":{"timestamp":" 947766918677"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766919376","data":{"timestamp":" 947766919376"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABAKE"," userResponse":" BABAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766920079","data":{"timestamp":" 947766920079"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766920905","data":{"timestamp":" 947766920904"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPEWA"," userResponse":" ALIPEWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766922101","data":{"timestamp":" 947766922101"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINA"," userResponse":" JINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766923005","data":{"timestamp":" 947766923005"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUAMBATA"," userResponse":" KIFO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766924865","data":{"timestamp":" 947766924864"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUAMBATA"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766926550","data":{"timestamp":" 947766926550"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUAMBATA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766927818","data":{"timestamp":" 947766927818"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766928514","data":{"timestamp":" 947766928514"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UREMBO"," userResponse":" UREMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766929343","data":{"timestamp":" 947766929342"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766931494","data":{"timestamp":" 947766931494"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIITWA"," userResponse":" ALIITWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766932180","data":{"timestamp":" 947766932180"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GRACA"," userResponse":" GRACA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766934232","data":{"timestamp":" 947766934231"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALIITWA"," userResponse":" UREMBO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766938870","data":{"timestamp":" 947766938870"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ALIITWA"," userResponse":" START_KUAMBATA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766940707","data":{"timestamp":" 947766940706"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIITWA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766942207","data":{"timestamp":" 947766942206"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GRACA"," userResponse":" GRACA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766944014","data":{"timestamp":" 947766944014"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KADRI"," userResponse":" KADRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766944647","data":{"timestamp":" 947766944646"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIAKA"," userResponse":" MIAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766945726","data":{"timestamp":" 947766945725"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIPOZIDI"," userResponse":" ILIPOZIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766946718","data":{"timestamp":" 947766946717"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUYOYOMA"," userResponse":" KUYOYOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766947751","data":{"timestamp":" 947766947751"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIVYO"," userResponse":" NDIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766948366","data":{"timestamp":" 947766948365"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GRACA"," userResponse":" GRACA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766949216","data":{"timestamp":" 947766949216"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIZIDI"," userResponse":" ALIZIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766949848","data":{"timestamp":" 947766949847"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULETA"," userResponse":" KULETA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766950781","data":{"timestamp":" 947766950780"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766951366","data":{"timestamp":" 947766951366"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAO"," userResponse":" KWAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766955297","data":{"timestamp":" 947766955296"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KADRI"," userResponse":" KADRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766956204","data":{"timestamp":" 947766956204"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIAKA"," userResponse":" MIAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766956975","data":{"timestamp":" 947766956974"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ILIPOZIDI"," userResponse":" START_ILIPOZIDI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766958422","data":{"timestamp":" 947766958422"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ILIPOZIDI"," userResponse":" WIKI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766960270","data":{"timestamp":" 947766960269"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIPOZIDI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766962321","data":{"timestamp":" 947766962321"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUYOYOMA"," userResponse":" KULETA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766963755","data":{"timestamp":" 947766963755"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUYOYOMA"," userResponse":" WIKI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766965474","data":{"timestamp":" 947766965473"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUYOYOMA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766966245","data":{"timestamp":" 947766966245"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NDIVYO"," userResponse":" KUYOYOMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766967381","data":{"timestamp":" 947766967381"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIVYO"," userResponse":" NDIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766968082","data":{"timestamp":" 947766968082"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GRACA"," userResponse":" GRACA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766969399","data":{"timestamp":" 947766969399"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIZIDI"," userResponse":" ALIZIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766970989","data":{"timestamp":" 947766970989"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULETA"," userResponse":" KULETA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766971574","data":{"timestamp":" 947766971574"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FURAHA"," userResponse":" FURAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766972183","data":{"timestamp":" 947766972183"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAO"," userResponse":" KWAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766974257","data":{"timestamp":" 947766974256"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" FAMILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766975424","data":{"timestamp":" 947766975423"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIAMUA"," userResponse":" ILIAMUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766976223","data":{"timestamp":" 947766976223"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMPA"," userResponse":" KUMPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766976839","data":{"timestamp":" 947766976838"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GRACA"," userResponse":" GRACA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766977650","data":{"timestamp":" 947766977649"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASOMO"," userResponse":" MASOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766978859","data":{"timestamp":" 947766978858"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZURI"," userResponse":" MAZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766980524","data":{"timestamp":" 947766980523"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" WIKI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766983164","data":{"timestamp":" 947766983163"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" GRACA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766984952","data":{"timestamp":" 947766984952"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAMILIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766986637","data":{"timestamp":" 947766986636"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ILIAMUA"," userResponse":" MASOMO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766987986","data":{"timestamp":" 947766987985"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIAMUA"," userResponse":" ILIAMUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766988665","data":{"timestamp":" 947766988665"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMPA"," userResponse":" KUMPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766989577","data":{"timestamp":" 947766989577"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GRACA"," userResponse":" GRACA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766990499","data":{"timestamp":" 947766990499"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MASOMO"," userResponse":" START_MASOMO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766991378","data":{"timestamp":" 947766991378"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MASOMO"," userResponse":" START_MASOMO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766993205","data":{"timestamp":" 947766993204"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MASOMO"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947766997966","data":{"timestamp":" 947766997966"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MAZURI"," userResponse":" START_MAZURI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767001846","data":{"timestamp":" 947767001846"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Familia iliamua kumpa Graca masomo mazuri."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZURI"," userResponse":" MAZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767004288","data":{"timestamp":" 947767004287"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GRACA"," userResponse":" GRACA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767005279","data":{"timestamp":" 947767005278"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITIA"," userResponse":" ALITIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767005806","data":{"timestamp":" 947767005806"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BIDII"," userResponse":" BIDII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767006353","data":{"timestamp":" 947767006353"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767007135","data":{"timestamp":" 947767007133"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULENI"," userResponse":" SHULENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767008922","data":{"timestamp":" 947767008922"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GRACA"," userResponse":" GRACA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767009666","data":{"timestamp":" 947767009666"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ALITIA"," userResponse":" SHULENI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767010767","data":{"timestamp":" 947767010767"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITIA"," userResponse":" ALITIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767015500","data":{"timestamp":" 947767015500"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" BIDII"," userResponse":" START_ALITIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767022116","data":{"timestamp":" 947767022116"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BIDII"," userResponse":" BIDII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767022120","data":{"timestamp":" 947767022120"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767022720","data":{"timestamp":" 947767022720"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULENI"," userResponse":" SHULENI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767024723","data":{"timestamp":" 947767024722"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPATA"," userResponse":" ALIPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767025481","data":{"timestamp":" 947767025481"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUZO"," userResponse":" TUZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767026263","data":{"timestamp":" 947767026263"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBALO"," userResponse":" AMBALO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767027493","data":{"timestamp":" 947767027492"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINGEBADILISHA"," userResponse":" LINGEBADILISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767028538","data":{"timestamp":" 947767028537"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAISHA"," userResponse":" MAISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767029149","data":{"timestamp":" 947767029148"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767033360","data":{"timestamp":" 947767033360"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPATA"," userResponse":" ALIPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767034085","data":{"timestamp":" 947767034085"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUZO"," userResponse":" TUZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767034791","data":{"timestamp":" 947767034790"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBALO"," userResponse":" AMBALO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767035710","data":{"timestamp":" 947767035710"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LINGEBADILISHA"," userResponse":" BIDII"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767038265","data":{"timestamp":" 947767038265"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" LINGEBADILISHA"," userResponse":" TUZO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767040361","data":{"timestamp":" 947767040360"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINGEBADILISHA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767042626","data":{"timestamp":" 947767042626"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAISHA"," userResponse":" MAISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767042872","data":{"timestamp":" 947767042872"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767045133","data":{"timestamp":" 947767045133"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767046205","data":{"timestamp":" 947767046205"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UHISANI"," userResponse":" UHISANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767047145","data":{"timestamp":" 947767047145"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKUSOMEA"," userResponse":" WAKUSOMEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767047629","data":{"timestamp":" 947767047628"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767048622","data":{"timestamp":" 947767048621"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NZURI"," userResponse":" NZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767049522","data":{"timestamp":" 947767049522"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJNI"," userResponse":" KIJIJNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767052400","data":{"timestamp":" 947767052399"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767053768","data":{"timestamp":" 947767053767"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" UHISANI"," userResponse":" SHULE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767056328","data":{"timestamp":" 947767056328"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" UHISANI"," userResponse":" WAKUSOMEA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767058058","data":{"timestamp":" 947767058057"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UHISANI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767060113","data":{"timestamp":" 947767060113"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAKUSOMEA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767061573","data":{"timestamp":" 947767061572"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAKUSOMEA"," userResponse":" SHULENI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767063422","data":{"timestamp":" 947767063421"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKUSOMEA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767064506","data":{"timestamp":" 947767064506"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" NZURI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767065692","data":{"timestamp":" 947767065690"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" ALITIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767067200","data":{"timestamp":" 947767067200"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHULE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767068389","data":{"timestamp":" 947767068389"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NZURI"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767069343","data":{"timestamp":" 947767069343"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NZURI"," userResponse":" NZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767070154","data":{"timestamp":" 947767070154"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJIJNI"," userResponse":" KIJIJNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767071916","data":{"timestamp":" 947767071916"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOTO"," userResponse":" NDOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767072443","data":{"timestamp":" 947767072443"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767073474","data":{"timestamp":" 947767073473"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767073974","data":{"timestamp":" 947767073973"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767074463","data":{"timestamp":" 947767074463"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767075314","data":{"timestamp":" 947767075314"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWALIMU"," userResponse":" MWALIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767076941","data":{"timestamp":" 947767076941"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDOTO"," userResponse":" NDOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767077307","data":{"timestamp":" 947767077307"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767078227","data":{"timestamp":" 947767078227"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767078420","data":{"timestamp":" 947767078420"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767079637","data":{"timestamp":" 947767079637"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767080745","data":{"timestamp":" 947767080745"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWALIMU"," userResponse":" MWALIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767083265","data":{"timestamp":" 947767083264"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITAMANI"," userResponse":" ALITAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767083996","data":{"timestamp":" 947767083996"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767084211","data":{"timestamp":" 947767084210"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767085239","data":{"timestamp":" 947767085238"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOZAMBIQUE"," userResponse":" MOZAMBIQUE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767086061","data":{"timestamp":" 947767086060"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAJUE"," userResponse":" WAJUE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767086800","data":{"timestamp":" 947767086800"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767087049","data":{"timestamp":" 947767087048"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767087995","data":{"timestamp":" 947767087994"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUANDIKA"," userResponse":" KUANDIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767095025","data":{"timestamp":" 947767095025"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITAMANI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767097289","data":{"timestamp":" 947767097289"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" MWALIMU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767100456","data":{"timestamp":" 947767100456"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" KUANDIKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767102150","data":{"timestamp":" 947767102150"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767103524","data":{"timestamp":" 947767103524"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" ALITAMANI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767105769","data":{"timestamp":" 947767105769"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767105861","data":{"timestamp":" 947767105860"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MOZAMBIQUE"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767107813","data":{"timestamp":" 947767107812"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MOZAMBIQUE"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767109603","data":{"timestamp":" 947767109603"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOZAMBIQUE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767109894","data":{"timestamp":" 947767109894"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAJUE"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767110900","data":{"timestamp":" 947767110900"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAJUE"," userResponse":" GRACA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767112417","data":{"timestamp":" 947767112417"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAJUE"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767113563","data":{"timestamp":" 947767113562"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" START_NZURI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767118995","data":{"timestamp":" 947767118995"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" START_KUSOMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767120433","data":{"timestamp":" 947767120432"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767121503","data":{"timestamp":" 947767121503"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767122483","data":{"timestamp":" 947767122483"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KUANDIKA"," userResponse":" MAISHA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767125727","data":{"timestamp":" 947767125727"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUANDIKA"," userResponse":" KUANDIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767127119","data":{"timestamp":" 947767127118"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947767127234","data":{"timestamp":" 947767127233"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000113_153306"," gameId":" 3a4ef253-54ba-49d5-8721-9058e38c280b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitamani wakati ambapo watoto wote wangeenda shuleni."," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUANDIKA"," userResponse":" KUANDIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}